你有没有看见
Did you see that caption
我在轩尼诗募捐会那张照片下的标题
underneath the photo of me from the Hennessy fundraiser?
谁是真正的第一夫人 就是性别歧视
Who's the real first lady? Sexist bullshit.
不要跟他们计较
Can't get drawn into it.
比较了我们的服装预算和设计师...
Comparing our clothing budgets and our stylists...
好像我们只注重这些一样
Like that's all we care about?
还有那个叫Mark Rivera的 居然在专栏说我是天后
And that Mark Rivera called me a diva in his column.
那个蠢侏儒
Stupid fucking midget.
显然他没听你唱过
Clearly he hasn't heard you sing.
他是个混蛋
The guy's a dick.
嘿 Gary 帮我选好狗没
Gary, did you find me a dog yet?
好了 这里有几个候选
Yeah, I selected a few candidates.
或者我该说候选狗?
Or should I say canine-didates?
不 你不用那么说
No, you shouldn't say that.
我看看  这个怎么样
Let me see. - What do you think of that?
梗犬? 对啊
a terrier? - Yeah.
不行 梗犬是天后狗 排除
No way. A terrier is a diva dog. Forget it.
我才不要那种吵吵嚷嚷的小毛球 每30分钟还要拉一次屎
I don't need a ball of yappy hair shitting its body weight every 30 minutes.
那你想要猫吗 我可以帮你找只猫
Do you want a cat? I can get you a cat.
不 不 我觉得自己是个坏妈妈 知道吗
No, no. I feel like a bad mom, you know?
Catherine小的时候我从不让她养狗
'Cause I never let Catherine get a dog when she was little.
这是我们的新起点
This is a fresh start for us.
从零开始做父母
It's parental ground zero.
瞧瞧这个
Look at this.
哥伦比亚特区20年 恭喜
20 years in D.C. Congratulations.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们都不吃菠萝的吧
I didn't think you guys would eat the pineapple.
听着 你养了狗 对不对
Listen, you're a dog person, right?
养的什么品种  我养了只真的狗
What kind of dog do you have? - I have a real dog.
Simon 黑色拉布拉多
Simon, black labrador.
Simon? 真是个难以置信的名字
Simon? What an unbelievable name.
我觉得他看起来就像个Simon
I guess he just looked like a Simon.
继续 拿照片出来看看 Mike
Go on, get the photo out, Mike.
不要看照片吧
I don't think we need to see the photo.
噢 我想看照片
I'd love to see a photo.
好吧  我看看
Sure. - Let me see.
皮毛真亮 是不是
Such a shiny coat, no?
怎么保养的 Mike
How do you get that coat so shiny, Mike?
呃 用水 很多水
Keep him hydrated. Lots of water.
知道吧  是喝还是拿来洗澡
you know? - to drink or applied directly to The coat?
哈 离老子的假狗远点
Leave my fake dog alone.
我刚在想
You know, I was just thinking,
我们可以养搜救犬 效果不错的
maybe we should get a rescue dog 'cause it'll play great.
只要不是三只脚再加个轮子的就行
As long as it's not one of those animals with three legs and a wheel.
好  四只脚 可以 三只脚 不行
- Yeah. - Four legs good, three legs bad.
知道了  干啥呢 90年代末都这样打招呼
- I got it. - Whassup, as they say in the late '90s?
嘿 Jonah 总统有没有取消中国总理的日程
Hey, Jonah. Did the President cancel the Chinese premier
他会来我的二十周年庆么 不 女士
- to come to my 20th party? - No, ma'am.
他肯定不会错过您的聚会
Although I'm sure he wouldn't miss it for the world
如果不是因为他对世界举足轻重
if it weren't for the fact that he runs the world.
肯定的是 就算他出席了 也缓解不了您和第一夫人间的不和
I'm sure his absence has nothing to do with your rift with the first lady.
什么 我们没有不和
What? There is no rift.
只是一个小小 小小的分歧
It was one tiny, little disagreement
每个人都搞得像是打了架一样
and everyone's making it out like we had a catfight
我们在地图室
in the map room or something.
话说 她打架会很凶狠
She'd be a rough fighter, though.
她肩膀超宽的 且不是因为垫肩
She's got big shoulders. Those aren't pads.
噢 女士 总统想确认下 你什么时候会宣布
Ma'am, potus also wanted to know when you would be announcing
石油产业人员进绿色产业工作小组的事
the oil guy that's gonna be going on the clean jobs task force.
Mike大哥在跟进  今天会吗 还是明天
- This bozo Mike's on it. - So today? Tomorrow?
听得懂就眨个眼 Mike  哈哈
Blink if you understand me, Mike....
至于那个不和谣言嘛 我会时刻竖起耳朵
And as regards to the rift rumors, I'll keep my ear to the ground for you.
小心耳朵别掉了
Be careful your ears don't pop on the way down.
好了 大家现在能进来吗
Okay, can everybody come in here, please?
可以  来吧
Sure. - come on.
我们要堵住谣言
Right, we're gonna have to shut down this story
关于我和第一夫人不和
about me and the first lady.
所以 这个庆典不能太以我为中心
I mean, it means we're gonna have to undiva my party.
也就是说 我的那些大照片不能摆出来了
We're gonna have to lose those huge photos of me.
不 我喜欢那些照片  我知道 都照得很好
- No, I like those. - I know, they're great photos.
我知道 但是我们不能要
I know, but there's no way we can have them.
这主意不错 我们不想你看起来像...
It's a good idea. We don't want you to look like...
斯大林
Stalin.
我其实想说贝隆夫人
I was gonna say Eva Peron.
对 这个比喻好点 没胡子
Yeah, I prefer that comparison. Less of a mustache.
实际怎样知道吗 她挺时髦的
And you know what, actually? She was kind of chic.
怎一个美字了得  嗯 长得像麦当娜
Gorgeous. - Mmhmm. looks Like Madonna.
是的
Yeah.
Mike 任命Chuck的报道出来了吗
Mike, have you announced Chuck yet?
我还在做 Amy  噢 拜托
- I'm still working on it, Amy. - Come on.
这又不是胡佛水坝  这就是胡佛水坝…
- This is not the Hoover dam. - Yeah, it is the Hoover dam...
豆腐渣工程
Filled with shit.
一旦任命那个Chuck Furnham 前石油产业人员
And when we announce Chuck Furnham, an ex-oil guy,
进入绿色产业小组工作
on the clean jobs task force,
知道随后会发生什么吗 Amy
do you know what happens with all that shit, Amy?
呃 会习惯你既不恰当又不愉快的比喻么
Does it get used in a clumsy and unpleasant analogy by you?
Amy 石油业本来就不喜欢我 我们堵住了税收漏洞
Look, Amy, oil already hates me 'cause we're closing their tax loopholes
让他们为绿色产业买单 现在我是众矢之的
and making them pay for cleanup, so now I'm eating everyone's shit.
我就像是人体蜈蚣里面 排最后的那个人
I'm like the last guy in a human centipede with this.
不恰当比喻又来了
And there it is.
我们只要放一个人进小组
We just got to put one guy on clean jobs.
Chuck是石油业的 但他不是坏的那种
Chuck's oily, but he's not evil oily.
他是前石油业  对 你今天要发出来
- He's ex-oil. - Yeah, you put it out today.
今天? 半个哥伦比亚特区都在出席 Reeves参议员的剪彩仪式
Today? Half of D.C. is at Senator Reeves' dedication ceremony.
那就在那儿发布
Well, then you put it out there.
虽然这样很失礼 不过你是对的
I thought it might be disrespectful, but you're right.
他是Rapey Reeves 那家伙什么时候有礼了
He was rapey Reeves. When was that guy ever respectful?
好 您女儿两小时内会到
Okay, your daughter gets here in two hours.
天 今天就是个完美风暴 觉不觉得
God, today feels like the perfect storm, doesn't it?
对 飓风Selina
Yeah, hurricane Selina.
对 啊噢 等等
Yeah. Uh oh, wait a minute.
是不是真的有飓风Selina
Does that exist, hurricane Selina?
噢 我不...  能查查吗
- I don't... - Can we run a check on that?
在查了
I'm binging it.
太挤了 Dan和Jonah 请出去
Too full. Dan and Jonah out, please.
你们要知道 如果是在救生艇上 也会这么安排
And just so you know, this is also what would happen if we were in a lifeboat.
你不会信的
You're not gonna believe this.
Selina就在明年的飓风单上
Selina is on next year's list of hurricanes.
噢 该死
Shit!
万一它登陆了 出个头条说
What if it hits and we get headlines
Selina造成大规模破坏 怎么办
saying Selina causing large-scale devastation?
人们不会把您跟自然灾害归类的 女士
People won't equate you with a natural disaster, ma'am.
真的吗 Amy 因为我遇到一些人
Really, Amy? 'Cause I've met some people, okay?
真的人 我实在是要说
Real people, and I've got to tell you,
大部分都是群傻逼
a lot of them are fucking idiots.
噢 天呐 你看到没
Oh my God. Do you see this?
Reeves参议员娱乐中心
The Senator Reeves Recreation Center.
你知道那笨手笨脚老爷爷根本不能游泳吗
Did you know old grandpa fumblepants couldn't even swim?
他只能在浅水区看着别人
He would just hang out in the shallow end and stare.
你知道他最喜欢哪里中风吗
You know what his favorite stroke was?
难道是鸡鸡  就是鸡鸡
Was It dick stroke? - It Was dick stroke.
哦 寡妇来了 寡妇来了
Widow, widow, widow.
他是个那么好的人  谢谢 Selina
- He was such a wonderful man. - Thank you so much, Selina.
哦 看这里 他真开心
Look at him here. He is so happy.
关于你和第一夫人的事 我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your feud with the first lady.
噢 你知道的...
You know...
她真的挖走你的设计师吗
Is it true that she stole your stylist?
没有 你知道的 报纸就是...
No. You know, the newspapers just make...
打扰下 女士 总统来电话了
Sorry, ma'am. This is the President calling.
不能让他等  噢 这个要接
- It just can't wait. - I have to take this.
我先走开一下  好的
will you excuse me? - Go ahead.
喂 对 嗨 总统先生
Hello? Yes. Hi, Mr. President.
供您参考 女士 其实总统没打电话
F.Y.I., ma'am, the President is not calling.
供你参考 Gary 废话少说  好
- F.Y.I., Gary, no shit. - Okay.
宣布Chuck的任命没  我在等最好的时机 好吧
- Is Chuck announced yet? - I'm waiting for the perfect time, okay?
你就像个...
You are like a...
耳垂...就在那里
Earlobe... you're just there,
摇摆不定
just wobbling.
Doyle就在那儿  我知道
Doyle is Right there. - I know.
现在说  我会的
do It now. - I will.
Doyle参议员  不要
Senator Doyle. - Stop.
Mike有话要说 如果您不介意的话
- Mike wanted a word, if you don't mind. - Mike McClintock.
最近好吗  对 先生 很好 先生
- You are well? - Yes, sir. Very good, sir.
噢 娘的 这蘑菇真好吃
Holy shit. These mushrooms are amazing.
你想说什么 Mike  肯定加了意大利奶酪什么的
- What is it, Mike? - Must be ricotta or something in there.
哦 真好笑  对啊
- That's funny. - Yeah.
真好 我喜欢幽默  对
- Goody, I love humor. - Yeah.
我这儿有个假设  嗯
I have a hypothetical for you. - Okay.
如果我们让Chuck Furnham 加入绿色产业小组 您觉得怎样
What would you say if we announced Chuck Furnham to the clean jobs task force?
Furnham?  对 Chuck
- Furnham? - Yeah, Chuck.
那就算副总统背叛了我们
Well, that would be a betrayal from the veep.
不一定吧
Not necessarily.
那我应该会把猿粪和蝙蝠屎混在一起
So I imagine that I would mix ape shit with bat shit,
用怨念举起它
raise it to a whole new level of fury,
然后撕了你的脸
then I'd probably rip your face off
拿你的眼窝做性玩具
and use your eye sockets as a sex toy.
就是个假设 跟你的一样
It's just a hypothetical like yours.
Chuck就是打了石油的标签而已
Chuck would just be token oil.
石油业以为他是特洛伊木马
Oil would think he's their trojan horse,
其实他是个空心马
he'd be a hollow horse.
也不算空心马 他还是特洛伊木马
Not a hollow horse. That's a trojan horse.
但是个特洛伊空心马 先生
He'd be a hollow trojan horse, sir.
你们承诺过不会有石油业的人
I was promised no one from oil.
Chuck不是石油业的 他去年退休了  对 从石油业退的
- Chuck's not oil. He retired a year ago. - Yeah, from oil.
现在 我他妈一定要去跟副总统聊聊  好吧
Now I fucking want to speak to The Vice President. - Okay.
飓风预告效果不错
Hurricane forecast is looking good,
您女儿刚刚也到达办公室了
and your daughter's just arrived at the office.
太好了 这是我们的暗号  Hallowes 飓风Hallowes
- Great, that's our cue. - Hallowes, hurricane Hallowes.
嗨 你好  Barbara 你好
Hi. Hello. - Barbara. Hello.
不好意思 Hallowes参议员
I am so sorry, Senator Hallowes.
总统打电话来了  噢 亲爱的 对不起
- The President is calling. - Oh dear. I'm sorry.
等我一下哦
Excuse me just for one second.
听着 在你打假电话的时候
Listen, while you take your fake phone call,
我应该可以把Dan偷来一下吧
is it okay if I steal Dan for a second?
或者说是偷回来?
Or should I say steal Dan back?
您能等一下吗
Could you hold on just one second?
知道吗 事实上 这个电话不是假的
You know what? Actually, this phone call is not fake.
Dan是个自由个体 他想去哪就去哪
And Dan is his own man. He can go wherever he wants.
好的 这边请Dan  让你等久了 总统先生
- Okay. This way, Dan. - I'm sorry to keep you holding, Mr. President.
知道什么是天后吗 那个才他妈是天后
You know who's a fucking diva? That's a fucking diva.
就是她
That one.
大学生活怎么样  挺好的
- So how's college? - It's good.
除开特勤处保卫人员什么的 我觉得自己...
You know, except for the whole secret service detail, I think I'm actually...
副总统办公室  开始融入进去了
- Office of the Vice President. - ...Starting to blend in.
不是 午餐时间当然是吃午饭
No, at lunchtime she eats lunch.
再见  选好新狗了吗
Good-bye. Have you chosen a new dog yet?
什么狗
What dog?
你妈妈要养狗 如果这还是秘密 我道歉
Your mom is getting a dog. Apologies if that was a secret.
副总统办公室
Office of the Vice President.
你发短信甩了我女儿 连个道歉都没
You dumped my daughter by text and didn't even apologize.
没 我道了 我打了个苦脸表情
No, I did. I signed off with colon open brackets.
听着 Selina真准备用Chuck Furnham 来安抚石油业游说团吗
Listen, is Selina really trying to appease the oil lobby with Chuck Furnham?
我猜Chuck可以看做是一种手势 -
I suppose Chuck could be viewed as a gesture.
Chuck就是这种手势
Chuck is a gesture all right.
知道石油业怎么叫他的吗
Do you know what these oil wise guys call him?
叫他 谁他妈是Chuck Furnham
They call him who the fuck is Chuck Furnham?
Chuck Furnham本来是12:15来的 但是他12:00就到了
Chuck Furnham's at 12:15. Now he's at 12:00.
现在他在这儿
Now he's here.
副总统女士  Chuck 你好吗
Madam Vice President. - Chuck!How are you?
他们说我会加入绿色产业
I was promised movement on the clean jobs.
对的 就我俩知道哦 我们可能
Yes. Between us, we might possibly
会在今天宣布你的任命
make your announcement today.
好 好  是啊 好
Yes. Yes. - Yes. right.
太好了  噢 天
Fantastic. - My.
谢谢 女士  还有
- Thank you, ma'am. - And, you know,
我一见到他们就有这个想法了
I've been thinking ever since I saw them,
你的孙子 Marion和… Richard.
your grandchildren, Marion and... - Richard.
对 Richard 我这儿有副总统牌m&ms豆 (巧克力豆)
Yes, Richard. And I have some vice presidential M&Ms
想送给他们
that I would love for them to have.
看到这个印章了吗 我们这还要一盒
You see the seal right there? Except we'll need another one
有两个孙子呢
because there are two grandchildren.
没了  没了?
- I'm out. - You're out?
没了  噢 哼 真遗憾
- I'm out. - Well, that's a shame.
不知道为什么会这样 好吧
I don't know how that happened. Okay.
太感谢你了   不用谢
- Thank you so much. - You're so welcome.
醒醒吧 Dan 这是石油业
Wake up, Dan. This is oil.
你一旦任命Chuck Furnham
You nominate Chuck Furnham, and these guys
他们就会拿把铲子铲掉他的头
will fucking take his head off with a shovel.
Selina得换个人
Selina needs to find somebody else.
你喜欢这儿 我很高兴
I'm glad you enjoyed yourself.
Carol Hallowes 嗨
Carol Hallowes, hi.
噢Reeves夫人 对于您的失夫之痛 我很遗憾
Mrs. Reeves, I am so sorry for your loss.
您丈夫是个有力的竞赛者
Your husband was a massive player.
当然 是从政治上说
Politically speaking, of course.
我叫Jonah
I'm Jonah.
我在白宫工作...  你还好吧 女士
- I work at the White House. - Are you okay, ma'am?
噢 对不起 我都没意识到 你还好吧
I'm sorry. I didn't even realize. Are you okay?
你能帮我拿杯水来吗
Could you please get me a glass of water?
可是 这里没服务员啊 至少我没看见
You know what? There aren't any waiters, at least that I've seen.
Jonah 你能帮她拿杯水来吗
Jonah, would you please get her a glass of water?
当然 当然了
Absolutely. Of course. Of course.
我以为脱水了就没眼泪了
I guess all those tears must be dehydrating.
我不这么觉得
I don't think it works like that.
我还是去拿水吧 好吗
You know, I'll just get the water, okay?
你他妈的寡妇
Cock-blocking widow.
Doyle参议员否定了Chuck
Senator Doyle went black swan over Chuck.
他说我们承诺过不要石油业的
He says we promised him no oil.
我对Chuck说任命今天会下来
I implied to Chuck that we would announce today.
该死 他有可能老得不记得了么
Shit. Is he senile enough to forget?
嘿  嘿 Hallowes怎么说
How was Hallowes?
Dan 嗨 我讨厌Chuck Furnham
Dan, hi. I hate Chuck Furnham.
等等 什么
Wait, what?
对 她还预言了石油业所有的激烈反应
Yeah, she's predicting all kinds of backlash from oil.
为什么石油业会不喜欢Chuck Furnham
How could oil not like Chuck Furnham?
因为他还不够油  噢
He's not oily enough....
没关联的 一切我们喜欢他的理由 他们都讨厌
Unconnected. For all the reasons that we loved him, they hate him.
所以我们现在同时有两个两难抉择了
Okay, so now we have two catch-22 situations simultaneously.
不会还有专门说这种情况的词吧
Is there even a name for that?
四难抉择怎么样
- How about catch-44? - Gary.
好吧 我去找石油业说客聊聊
Okay, I'm gonna run it by an oil lobbyist.
Sidney Purcell就在那儿  噢 真好
- Sidney Purcell is right there. - Oh, good.
去吧 Amy 上  好
- Do that, Amy. Go. - Okay.
大部分庆典照片都要拿走
Well, most of the party photos need to be removed.
我不知道 用你的直觉
I don't know. Use your instincts
眼睛 然后还有手跟胳膊
and your eyes, then your hands and arms. Thank you.
谢谢  我妈妈养狗这个决定真好
It's really nice that my mom's getting a new dog.
我一直想养狗
I always wanted a dog.
嘿 Catherine 你还要咖啡吗 还是...
Catherine, you want some more coffee?
不用 我还在喝这杯
No, I'm still drinking this one.
其实 你不用招待我的
You know, you don't have to entertain me.
我一个人发呆也挺好  噢 感谢上帝
- I'm cool with my own thoughts. - Oh, thank God.
电邮太多了 感觉心跳一下就来一封
'Cause I'm getting emails like every other heartbeat.
是啊
Yeah.
噢 嗨 Sidney 你好吗
Hi, Sidney. How are you?
噢 很好 吃了很多免费的虾
Good. You know, full of free shrimp.
嘿 我想跟你说说...绿色产业
Here's the thing... clean jobs.
绿色产业 对 那到底怎么回事
Clean jobs, yeah. What's going on there?
你们还没定好人吗 还是担心
You guys got a name yet? You too afraid
打印新闻稿会浪费地球资源
of wrecking the earth's resources to print up a press release?
我刚准备告诉你
I was actually gonna run a name by you.
别说Chuck Furnham
Don't say Chuck Furnham.
不准说Chuck Furnham
Do not say Chuck Furnham.
如果你说了Chuck Furnham 老子会过敏性休克的
If you say Chuck Furnham, I will go into anaphylactic fucking shock.
我是要说Chuck Furnham  你妈的
- I'm saying Chuck Furnham. - Fucking hell!
玩我呢 Chuck Furnham 这他妈算正式的了吗
Are you kidding me? Chuck Furnham? That's fucking official?
Chuck是石油业的  不 不 嘿 对不起 他不是
- Chuck is oil. - No. No, no, hey. I'm sorry, no.
他不算石油业 就是个他娘的老古董 但他不算石油业
He's not oil. He's a fucking fossil, but he's not oil.
我们要能拿来堵枪眼的人
We need somebody who is plugged in.
Chuck唯一能插入的就是他的小便袋
The only thing that Chuck is plugged into is his fucking piss bag.
我们会记录你的意见
Your comments are noted.
噢 真好 我喜欢被记录  谢谢
Good. I love being noted. - Thank you.
他说干掉Chuck  噢 上帝
he said Fuck Chuck. - God.
好吧 Chuck被否了 我们要让他闭嘴
Okay, Chuck is dead and we're gonna just have to keep him quiet
因为这个地方到处都是
because this whole place is swarming with bored reporters
又无聊又喜欢歪曲事实的记者
who are on pervert memorial duty.
所以你要做的 Mike 盯住他
So your job, Mike, is to keep him in your sight
直到我们找到代替者  好 他去哪儿了
- until we find a replacement. - Okay, where'd he go?
应该在卫生间  他的前列腺真是...
he must be in The bathroom. - that prostate of his.
进去 Mike 去
Get in there, Mike. Go.
再没比这更降低身份的了
This in no way will be demeaning.
假装你是去接他的 你就 当他是瞎子
Just pretend you're picking him up, you know, and he's blind.
危险 10点钟方向Doyle正在靠近
Mayday at 10:00. Senator Doyle is approaching.
Sidney Purcell也来了 5点方向
Sidney Purcell, too, 5:00.
Hallowes在你后面3象限 就在后面
Hallowes is in quadrant three right behind you, right behind you.
我们得跑路  找寡妇
- We've got to get out of here. - Widow walk.
别人不会冲你嚷嚷的
People don't shout at you
如果你站在刚死了老公的寡妇身边
when you're standing next to the dead man's grieving widow.
这主意好  Reeves夫人
- That's very good. - Mrs. Reeves.
Dan Egan 我为副总统做事
Dan Egan, I'm with the Vice President.
只想让你知道 我非常想念你的丈夫
I just wanted to tell you how much I thought of your husband.
谢谢 小伙子真帅
Well, thank you. What a handsome young man.
你也很迷人  你回来了
- Quite the wilf yourself. - You're back.
对 我回来了 不幸的是 我刚好要走了
Yes, I'm back. Unfortunately we're just about to leave.
不过 如果你能陪副总统出门...
But if you could perhaps walk the Vice President out to her car...
我很乐意 这样我们就有时间聊八卦了
Delightful. It will give us a chance for some juicy gossip.
好吧
- Okay. - Now is it true
听说第一夫人骂你讨厌鬼 真的假的
that the first lady calls you creepy veepy?
我很兴奋 再见
I'm very excited about it. Good-bye.
你兴奋什么 Chuck
What are you excited about, Chuck?
你要当路易威登的新代言人吗
Are you the new face of Louis Vuitton?
你把绿色产业小组的任命告诉别人了?
Have you been telling people about your appointment to clean jobs?
那有什么关系 副总统对我说 就快要宣布了
What's the problem? The Vice President told me it's as good as announced.
就快要 也就是 还没有
As good as announced is not announced.
你也快死了
You are as good as dead,
但你没死嘛...还没到时候
but you're not actually dead... Not yet.
好吧 Doyle和政党因为Chuck讨厌我
Okay, Doyle and the party hate me because of Chuck
石油产业因为Chuck讨厌我
and oil hates me because of Chuck.
第一夫人因为你比她漂亮才讨厌你
First lady hates you just because you're prettier.
对 但我们现在没在说这个 好吧
Yeah, that's not what we're talking about right now, okay?
谢了  不客气
- Thank you. - You're welcome.
我要时间 我还有时间吗 挤多点时间出来
I need time. Do I have time? Get me more time.
你要跟Catherine一起吃中饭
You're supposed to be having lunch with Catherine.
该死的 Gary 打电话给Sue  你想对她说什么
- Shit! Gary, call Sue. - What do you want me to tell her?
告诉她我要取消中饭 我安排它本来是想证明
Tell her that I'm canceling the lunch that was supposed to prove
没什么比Catherine更重要
there's nothing more important than Catherine
但现在 比Catherine更重要的事出现了
because something more important than Catherine has come up.
嗨 Sue  没关系 Gary 我能搞定
- Hi, Sue. - That's okay, Gary. I got all that.
好的  你妈妈随时有可能到
Okay. - your mom should be Here momentarily.
噢 她...  噢 我的乖乖女儿
- She's... - There's my girl!
我的女大学生  嗨 妈妈
- My college girl. - Hi, mother.
嗨 亲爱的 对不起 让你等久了 宝贝
Hi, darling. I'm sorry to keep you waiting, baby.
对不起  没关系
- I'm sorry. - It's okay.
我有Sue作伴 所以...  噢 真好
- I was just bonding with Sue. - Oh, good.
噢 Sue 总统打电话来了吗
Oh, Sue, did the President call?
没有  没有
No. - No.
呃 好吧 那 过来
Okay. Well, come.
来我的小床吧 我们可以在上面摇
Step into my crib. We can hang.
你们居然把我丢给色狼自己跑了 真他妈损
You guys ditched me at a pervert's memorial. That's some cold shit.
Catherine  嘿 哥们
- Catherine, hey. - Hey, buddy.
我们要谈谈
We need to talk.
所以我要开个小会
So I have to have a little meeting
看看到底发生了什么
to find out what the F-word is going on around here.
好  我们很快就开完 就这样
- Okay. - We'll do this quick. That's right.
Dan 在我们开紧急政治会议的时候
Dan, why don't you look after Catherine
要不你负责照顾下Catherine吧
while we attend to this urgent policy matter?
Dan 你没见过Catherine 你以前见过Catherine吗
Dan, you've never met Catherine. Have you met Catherine?
没有  不 你居然没有 过来 过来
- No. - No, you haven't. Come here. Come here.
来 过来 Catherine 这是Dan
Come, come. Catherine, this is Dan.
嗨  他在你妈妈办公室上班
- Hi. - He works in yo mama's office.
Hi. - Hi.
你不如跟Dan聊一聊
So why don't you tell Dan
你的 呃...
about the... you know, the...
实验戏剧课程?
Experimental theater course?
呃 对 是的
Sure. Yeah.
你可以跟他聊那个
You can talk to him about that.
你可以跟他什么都聊
You can talk about anything.
什么都聊  什么都聊
Anything. - Anything.
聊 聊 聊
Talk, talk, talk.
既然有许可说什么都可以聊...
Now that we have the permission to talk about anything...
你看过福克纳的作品么? (美国小说家)
Have you ever read Faulkner before?
一点点
A little bit.
Chuck Furnham走漏了消息
Chuck Furnham leaked.
现在我们有些什么选择 Mike?
Now what are our options, Mike?
听着 我不知道 好么? 就像是他妈的魔方一样
Look, I don't know, okay? It's like a fucking Rubik's cube.
我的意思是 到了这个地步已经无计可施了  什么 Mike?
- I mean, it's impossible at this point. - What, Mike?
魔方并不是无法破解的
A Rubik's cube is not impossible to solve.
我见过一个中国小孩10秒钟解开魔方
I saw a Chinese kid do it in like 10 seconds.
10秒钟 Mike
10 seconds, Mike.
让我深入想想 好么? 我需要点独处时间
Let me just have a deep think, okay? I need some me time.
让我好好想想
Just let me get deep.
他说得没错 我们是陷入困境了
He's not wrong. We are in a tight corner.
我想 这份工作的性质就是这样  噢 我可没在抱怨
- That's the nature of the job, I guess. - I'm not complaining.
我很高兴远离宠物狗和飓风
I am glad to be off dogs and hurricanes
回归原先愉悦的华盛顿暴风圈
and back in a good old Washington shit storm.
说到狗 那间房现在是什么情况?
Speaking of dogs, what's happening in that department?
交给我  好的
- I'm on it. - Okay.
你选好狗了么?
Have you reached a dog verdict yet?
你妈说最终决定权在你
Your mom said your decision is final.
是的 这条
Yeah, this one.
它看上去很震惊
Yeah, it looks astonished.
好像连着电缆线似的
Like it's attached to jumper cables or something.
我觉得他很可爱  好吧 是的 是的
- I think he's cute. - Okay, yeah. Yeah.
嗨大伙 宝贝 你要换衣服了
Guys. Honey, you've got to change.
或者穿这身 你要穿这身?
Or you're wearing that. Are you wearing that?
我是这么打算的 除非...
Yeah, I was planning on it, unless...
棒极了 很好 太好了
Great. Cool. Fantastic.
能让我们简短地聊聊么?
Can we have just a quick second to chat?
是的 当然  谢谢
- Yes, sure. - Thank you.
噢  我会离开
I will get out.
Amy 我能和你简短地聊聊么?
Amy, if I could just talk to you for a quick sec.
好的 可以
Okay. - if I could.
哦...没问题  谢谢 宝贝
- Yeah. Not a problem. - Thank you, darling.
那是条什么裙子? 一块地毯么?
What is that skirt? Is it a rug?
不 我想不是的 现在就是这种设计
No, I don't think so. I think they do that now.
她怎么样了? 还好么?
How is she? Is she good?
是的 她和平常没两样
Well, you know, y-yeah. She's her normal self.
真的非常好  很好
- Really great. - Oh, good.
有计划怎么解开魔方了么?
So do we have a plan to solve this Rubik's cube?
我一直在查看...  我有个主意
- I've been going over... - Here's an idea.
我们宣布领养一条狗 温和的晨间新闻
We announce the dog. It's soft wash,
但我们弄巧妙点
breakfast news, but we tease it out.
说我们想为它起个名
We say we're looking for a name.
会有成千上万的主意涌入
An ocean of ideas comes pouring in.
同时为我们赢得处理其他破事的时间
Meantime, we're buying time to figure all the other shit out.
这算是个好主意
That's kind of a great idea.
好的 她选了一条狗么?
Okay. - Did She choose a dog?
你他妈的开玩笑呢
Woof. - you got to be fucking kidding me.
我恨死这些动物
I hate these animals.
这个东西真是...萌到家了
This thing is... Unbelievably cute.
女士 Doyle参议员来了
Ma'am, Senator Doyle just arrived
表情就像是被爆菊了
and he has a face like he's been stabbed in the groin.
好吧 我现在没时间见他 因为现在我和女儿在一起
Okay. I can't talk to him 'cause I'm with my daughter.
也许上屋顶平台?  屋顶平台
Perhaps The widow walk? - The widow walk.
副总统女士  你就是寡妇(妻子站在屋顶平台望夫归家称活寡妇)
- Madam Vice President. - You're the widow.
跟我来 宝贝  你为什么无视我 女士?
- Come, honey. - Why are you ignoring me, ma'am?
我们假装...宝贝 别转头
We're gonna just pretend... Darling, don't turn around.
我已经来了  把头向我靠拢
- I've been here. - Just keep your head towards me.
就假装你和我在谈正事
Just pretend like you're talking seriously to me.
等等 妈妈 你的脸怎么了?  没什么 宝贝
- Wait, mom, what's wrong with your face? - Nothing, darling.
我是假装在和你说话  但我们是在说话
- I'm pretending to talk to you. - But we are talking.
不 不 我是说 这是假装...
No, no, I mean, it's a pretend...
夫人 你想我保证过
I was given your word, ma'am,
工作小组里没有石油背景的人
that nobody from oil was gonna be on the task force,
而现在这个叫Chuck的在胡说八道
and now I've got this Chuck bullshit.
Andrew 这整件事太微妙了
Andrew, this whole thing is so nuanced.
我要协调无数方的利益...
And I have a ton of interests that I have to square...
20年前 你没权力 但是你有胆量
20 years ago, you had no power, but you had balls.
现在看看你  是的 看看我
- Now look at you. - Yeah, now look at me.
我长了老二和睾丸 好么? (balls 胆量和睾丸双关)
I have a dick and balls, okay?
我们可不可以别...
Can we not have this...
不 别因为我而打断
No, please. Don't stop because of me.
这真的很有趣
This is really interesting.
嗨 我想我们没见过
Hi, I don't think we've had the chance to meet,
但我很高兴你在这
but I'm thrilled that you're here.
恭喜在华盛顿20年了  副总统夫人
- Congrats on 20 years in D.C. - Madam Vice President.
副总统决定收养一只被解救的动物
The Vice President has decided to adopt a rescue animal.
什么动物?  是一条狗
- What kind of animal? - It's a dog.
一条狗? 怎么 像你的狗一样么 Mike?
A dog? What, like your dog, Mike?
非常感谢
Thank you very much.
Andrew Miller 雨林保护协会的项目主管
Andrew Miller, program director at rainforest conservancy.
吹小号的  你做的事很重要
Plays The trumpet. - What important work you do.
可不仅仅是吹高音
And that's not just the high notes.
我将举办个独奏会  好的
I have a recital coming up. - Okay.
你可以说 别吹了 (双关 又有别搞砸的意思)  不 我可不会说的
- You could have said, don't blow it. - No, I'm not gonna say that.
瞧Gary
Look at Gary go.
他就像个聊天时的人工提词机
He's like a human teleprompter for small talk.
他自称Gary OK(对应卡拉OK)  太诡异了
- He calls this Gary-oke. - It's so weird.
就像是马语者似的
It's like he's the horse whisperer or something.
我可没说你妈是匹马
Not that I think your mother's a horse.
Jim Wiseman United Laminants和贵客
Jim Wiseman, United Laminants and guest.
是妻子 不是他女儿  妻子 不是女儿
Wife, not his daughter. Wife, not daughter.
Jim  副总统夫人 很高兴见到你
Jim. - Madam Vice President. good to See you.
妈妈的微笑快绷不住了
Mom's smile is starting to crack.
就像是她离婚时的脸
It's like her divorce face.
嘿 我也来自一个破碎的家庭
Oh, hey! I come from a broken home, too.
我觉得这个变故让我变得更专注
I found that the turmoil made me more focused,
更热情 更有决心得到我想要的
more passionate, more determined to get the things I want.
顺便提一下 我是Jonah 我在白宫西厢工作
I'm Jonah, by the way. I work at the west wing of the White House.
与什么对照 Graceland的西厢? (Graceland 猫王故居)
As opposed to what, the west wing of Graceland?
如果你愿意的话 我可以带你逛逛
I can get you a tour if you'd like.
我以前去过
Yeah, I've seen it before.
Jonah 西厢
Jonah, west wing.
养狗的通知情况如何 伙计?
So how'd the dog announcement go, buddy?
就像是培根长袍
Like a bacon burka.
培根长袍是什么意思?
What does that mean... bacon burka?
没什么 如果长袍是培根做的
Nothing. Just if burkas were made of bacon...
瞧 Mike是一条虚构的狗 这是华盛顿公开的秘密
See, it's kind of an open secret in Washington that Mike has an imaginary dog.
为什么?  逃避加班
Why? - Gets him out of staying late for work.
我们称他为胡扯帝  很天才
- We call it his bullshit-tzu. - That's kind of genius.
谢了 Todd  问题? 有问题?
- Thanks, Todd. - Problem? Problem?
泰坦尼克号甲板上的最后两人 是么?
Last two on the deck of the Titanic, huh?
是的 我想我可能还是跳船吧
Yeah, I think I might jump.
我可以看透你的上衣
You know, I can see right through your shirt.
是这么设计的么?  女士
- Is it designed that way? - Ma'am.
是的?  我们遇到个问题
Yes? - We have an issue.
白宫说他们希望你说句话
The White House says that they would like
让Sidney Purcell这类人
a, quote, Sidney Purcell- type figure
参与绿色产业小组
involved on clean jobs.
这个人  一帮混蛋
The person. - What a fistful of fucks.
你安排Sidney Purcell参加绿色产业 那就没戏了
You put Sidney Purcell on clean jobs, it's over.
死定了 没人能忍受
It's done. No one's gonna stomach that.
你有什么办法?
Well, what do you got?
我打算唬唬他们
I kind of want to call them out on their bluff.
我有个主意  什么...
I got something. - What...
Purcell先生 你好Dan Egan 副总统办公室的
Mr. Purcell. Hi, Dan Egan, vice President's office.
你好 Dan
Hi, Dan.
副总统很希望你加入绿色产业小组
The Vice President would love to have you on the clean jobs task force,
但我们都知道这么做结果很可怕
but we both know that would look fucking horrible.
谢谢
Thank you.
所以我们的建议是 Chuck继续留着
So what we're proposing is this, Chuck will stay on.
是么? 好吧 你就是来告诉我
Really? Okay, so you came over
你对我失望透顶
to tell me that you're disappointing the shit out of me.
我可不知道 你应该带个头 伙计
I didn't know that. You should have led with that, buddy.
但是...你将有和副总统沟通的私人渠道
But... you will have a private channel to the veep
了解所有和绿色产业相关的事情
on all clean job- related issues.
相比特别小组 你将对政策有更大的影响力
You'll have more influence over policy than the fucking task force.
我要和Catherine聊聊
I'm gonna go talk to Catherine.
她刚刚有了个新室友
She just got a new roommate.
不需要我女儿的简报 Gary
I don't need factoids about my daughter, Gary.
嗨 宝贝 瞧瞧你 一个人站在这
Hi, honey. Look at you. You're standing all by yourself.
我很好 妈妈
I'm fine, mom.
你饿么 亲爱的 你要吃东西么?
Are you hungry, love? Do you want food?
不 没关系 我已经吃过了  好吧
- No. It's okay. I already ate. - Okay.
瞧那 他们想拍个照
Look here. They want to take a picture.
神呐  我们合个影
- God. - Let's do that.
把你的饮料放下 宝贝
Yeah, put your drink down, babe.
妈妈 我真的很讨厌拍照  不 宝贝 你很美
- Mom, I really hate pictures. - No, honey, you're pretty.
现在微笑就好 微笑
Just smile now. Smile.
Catherine 我说真的 微笑 好么?
Catherine, I'm really serious. Smile, okay?
好了
There you go.
一定很好 很亲密
That's gonna be good. That's gonna be sweet.
我听说你有个新室友
I heard you have a new roommate.
是的 Dilka
Dilka.
Dilk...  什么?
Dilk... - What?
Dilka
Dilka. - Dilka?
我猜她爸是伊朗人  伊朗人?
- I think her dad's Iranian. - Iranian?
参议员 只想告诉你
Senator. Just wanted to let you know
你对Chuck Furnham这事发表的看法成功了
that your noise about Chuck Furnham did the trick.
他退出了  太好了
- He's off. - Well, that is great.
是的  怎么做到的?
Yeah. - How Did that happen?
石油公司气坏了
Well, oil was so pissed
我们竟然打算安排无足轻重的Chuck到特别小组
that we tried to put lightweight Chuck onto the task force
他们给总统施压 安排别人上位
that they forced the President to go with somebody else...
Sidney Purcell  操他妈的
Sidney Purcell. - Sweet hairy fuck.
我要和副总统聊聊
I need to speak to the Vice President.
好极了 非常感谢
That's great. Thank you so much.
飓风Selina 他们说可以改名
Hurricane Selina... they say they can change the name.
你逗我呢
You're kidding me.
这是天大的好消息  做得好
that is incredibly Great news. - Well done.
你要飓风改名?
You're changing the name of a hurricane?
是的 那会是我们的灾难
Yeah. And that would have been a disaster for us.
是的 自然如此 太吃惊了
Yeah, naturally. It's amazing.
你试图控制天气
You're trying to control the weather.
你可不是雷神
You are not fucking Thor, mom.
妈妈 我还是去做功课了
I'm just gonna go do my homework.
不 Catherine
No, Catherine, listen.
听着 这件事比你想得更复杂微妙
It a much more complicated and nuanced situation.
不 真的不是 你们这些应声虫从不会拒绝她么?
No, it's really not. Don't you yes-men ever say no to her?
他们当然会  是的 我们会
- Of course they do. - Yeah, we do. Yeah.
没错  好吧 你知道么?
- Exactly. - All right, you know what?
你有点失控了 跟我来
You're a little bit out of control.
失控?  是的
come with me. Yes. - out of control?
哎呦  不 别说哎呦 你知道这根本不痛
No, don't say ow. You know that didn't hurt.
进来 我要和你聊聊
Get into here. I need to talk to you for a second.
不是所有一切都围着你转
Not everything is always about you.
我知道不是 我知道
I know that everything isn't always about me. I know that.
你要飓风改名 妈妈
You're changing the name of a hurricane, mom.
就是这么办事的
This is how it works.
这是现实生活 一言难尽
This is real life. This is complicated.
这很微妙  微妙?
this is nuanced. - Nuanced?
你需要经验
You need experience.
妈妈 别他妈的像个政客一样和我说话
Mom, stop talking to me like a fucking politician.
我在努力 Catherine
I've been trying, Catherine.
我一整天都在努力和你聊天
I've been trying to talk to you this whole day.
聊什么?  任何东西
about What? - about everything.
我都不知道你有了新室友
I didn't even know that you had a new roommate.
还得他告诉我
What's-his-ass had to tell me.
我知道 Gary告诉你的
I know. Gary told you.
妈妈 你要做的就是开口问而已
All you have to do, mom, is ask.
说真的
Seriously.
好吧 这么做如何?
Okay. How about this?
听着 我们不打算让飓风改名了
Listen. We are not gonna change the name of the hurricane.
当然  谢谢 妈妈
- Sure. - Thank you, mom.
很抱歉我之前发火了
I'm sorry I got so upset before.
瞧她道歉了  不是问题
Look At Her apologizing. - Not a problem.
她会道歉是不是很好啊?  副总统女士
- Isn't she good to apologize? - Madam Vice President.
我们得聊聊  好的 有什么事?
We need to talk. - Okay. What Can I do for you?
你要把Chuck Furnham安排回特别小组
Well, you need to put Chuck Furnham back on the task force.
等等 我糊涂了 因为现在你求我
Wait, I'm confused, because now you're begging me
把当初要我从特别小组
to put back onto the task force
撤走的人 重新放回去
the same person you were begging me to take off of the task force.
当你大声说出来的时候 确实听上去...
When you say it out loud, you know, it does sound...
有点愚蠢
Kind of idiotic.
但是
Well, but it's
没目前的阻挠议案体系愚蠢
not as idiotic as the current filibuster system.
我可以想办法替你把Chuck Furnham 放回特别小组 没问题
I can find a way to get Chuck Furnham on the task force for you, no problem.
好极了  好极了
Super. - Super.
谢谢你 女士  那还用说
- Thank you, ma'am. - You betcha.
现在如何?
How about that?
好样的 Dan
Way to go, Dan.
第44条军规 他中招了 抱歉 (指陷入互相矛盾的境地)
Catch-44, he caught it. Pow! I'm sorry.
你们的人绿色产业小组都没问题了?
Are you guys all good on clean jobs?
Chuck Ham加入 还有什么?
Chuck ham is on and what?
还有Sidney Purcell会留下作为顾问
And Sidney Purcell will stay on as an advisor
非正式的职位
in an unofficial capacity....
好吧 勾掉  我们明天可以去领狗
All right. Tick it. - We Can pick up The dog tomorrow.
好极了
Oh, great!
抱歉 你们在说什么?
I'm sorry. What are you guys talking about?
我们要养条狗 没什么大事
We're getting a dog. It's no big deal.
为什么没人通知我这事?
Why wasn't I told about this?
为什么要通知你?
Why would you be told about that?
问题是 夫人 第一夫人目前正竭力想养一条狗
The thing is, ma'am, Flotus is currently procuring a canine for herself.
第一宠物狗 第一犬已经筹备了数周
The first dog, or F-dotus, has been planned for weeks.
我们不能允许你的狗风头盖过了第一犬
We simply can't allow the possibility that your dog will overshadow F-dotus.
别再说第一犬了  夫人 你必须杀了这只狗
- Stop saying F-dotus. - Ma'am, you need to kill the dog.
不是字面意思 但是 我的意思是 是的 如果到了这一步 那就是字面意思了
Not literally, but... I mean, yeah, if it comes to it, then literally.
不 杀了这只狗? 我们的狗  不 宝贝
- No! Kill the dog? Our dog? - No, honey.
Mike在哪 他在哪?
Where is Mike? Where is he?
又回去喂奶了
Back to his tits and dip.
你们真的要让这个长着强奸通缉犯样子的人
You guys, are we seriously gonna let the guy
指挥你们怎么做么?
with the police sketch face of a rapist tell us what to do?
这个强奸犯也许能进入8人团队
This rapist face gets eights.
你情我愿的 我也许能入选
Consensually, I might throw in.
我们为什么要灭了领狗新闻 我才刚刚宣布
Why are we killing the dog? I just announced it.
因为第一夫人要领狗 所以现在我不能领养了
Because the first lady is getting one, so now I can't get one.
为什么我不知道这件事  因为你太无能了
- Why don't I know this? - Because you're incompetent.
有个办法 Mike已经有了条狗
Here's an idea. Mike's already got a dog.
他有一整套装备 毛毯
He's got the whole setup for one... the blankets,
纸板箱 玩具球 所有的小玩具
the crate, the balls, all the little toys and stuff.
何不让他收下这条狗?  好主意
- Why doesn't he take the pooch? - That's a great idea.
不不  很好的解决方法 很好的解决方法
- Mm-mm, no, no. - Great solution. Great solution.
Simon是个雄性意识很强的狗
Simon is an Alpha male.
事实上我觉得这是个好主意
Actually, I think that is a good idea.
你们笑什么?  别说了 妈妈
- Why are you guys laughing? - Stop, mom.
说真的 Mike有一条虚构的狗
Seriously, Mike has a fake dog.
这里好像就你不知情
You're like the only one here who doesn't know that.
什么?
What?
是的 他借此逃避某些事情比如迟到挨批
Yeah, he uses it to get out of stuff like if he's late.
这就是所谓的牛头梗
It's called a shitbull terrier.
是胡扯帝  胡扯帝
- It's a bullshit-tzu. - Bullshit-tzu.
这是真的么 Mike?
Is this true, Mike?
这事有点难以收场了
It got a little out of hand.
你皮夹里放了一张照片 Mike
You carry a picture of it in your wallet, Mike.
我是谷歌搜索到的
I just got it from Google images.
我很抱歉夫人 我以为你知道 夫人
I'm sorry, ma'am. I thought you knew, ma'am.
不然我不会笑的  Gary知情?
Otherwise I would Not have been laughing. - Gary knew?
连他妈的Gary都知情?  好吧
Even fucking Gary knew? - Okay.
你要收下这条狗
You are getting the dog.
你要收下这条阴险的
You are getting this little rat-faced,
令人反感的 喜欢狗吠的小猎犬
repulsive, yappy, decrepit-looking terrier.
我真高兴你坦白了对
I'm glad that you were so honest
我选的这条狗的喜爱
about liking the one that I chose.
Catherine 我没有... 好吧 现在我要处理这件事了
Catherine, I didn't... okay, now I've got to deal with that situation.
所以真是太感谢了 Catherine
So thank you. Catherine.
也许现在我有真的借口了
Maybe I've got a real excuse now.
Sue的存在完全就是浪费  是的
- Sue's pretty wasted. - Yeah.
无可争议的第九人
And arguably a nine.
Sue. - Jonah.
你有空缺能让我上位么?
You got a convenient opening I can slide into?
为Jonah腾位置?
Open up a slot for Jonah?
这世上酒还不够多 Jonah
There's not enough alcohol in the world, Jonah.
你没说不行  不行!
- Didn't say no. - No!
嗨 夫人 要来一杯白葡萄酒么?  好的
- Ma'am, can I get you a glass of white wine? Okay. - Yeah.
Amy 你可以...
Amy, would you please...
把飓风的名字改了 已经做了
Get the hurricane name changed. Already done it.
很好
Good.
这个晚宴没有太失控 是么?
It's not too diva-like, this party, is it?
是的 我觉得我们的基调正合适
No, I think we got just the right tone.
是的  大家显然没有太享受
- Yeah. - People definitely aren't having too much fun.
好了 给你
Okay, here we go.
给你  谢谢
there. - Thank you.
干杯
Bottoms up.
你要应酬了么?  是的
- So, you want to mingle? - Yeah.
我们去应酬这群人吧
Let's go mingle the shit out of 'em.
救生船协会的 Ernest Lainchbury先生
Ernest Lainchbury, Lifeboat Association.
他有一个玻璃假眼  我...
- He's got a glass eye. - I...
很高兴见到你
Am so happy you're here.
全美残疾人运动协会的 Jenny Armitage
Jenny Armitage, Disabled Sports of America.
刚刚得了三胞胎  三胞胎
just had triplets. - triplets.
一定很痛...除非你剖腹产
That must have hurt... Unless you had a C-section.
Carlos Esquerra 纳斯达克o.m.x集团的CEO
Carlos Esquerra, C.E.O. of the Nasdaq O.M.X. group.
我一无所知 说西班牙语
I got nothing. Use your Spanish.
Su casa es mi casa. - mi casa.
Mi casa es su casa.
Robert Van De Merkle 博彩协会主席
Robert Van Der Merkle, head of Gambling Commission.
赞成赌博 喜欢射击
Pro-gambling. Loves to kill.
你好
There.
Corey Wilk 密西根最高法院的特别顾问
Corey Wilk, special advisor to the Supreme Court of Michigan.
他有个兄弟是rage against the machine乐队成员
He's got a brother in Rage Against the Machine.
告诉你兄弟 我喜欢他的音乐 -
Tell your brother I love his music.
社会行动中心的Carrie Stringer
Carrie Stringer, Center for Social Action.
他是三项全能运动员  不 他不是
- He's a triathlete. - No, he's not.
你好
Hello.
Liam Miller, NASA.
好的 这是美国宇航局的缩写...
Okay, that's an acronym for National Aeronautics...
别说了  好吧
I... stop it. - Okay.
已经很晚了
It's so late.
活着的耶稣基督教会的Terrance Clark牧师
The Reverend Terrance Clark, Church of the Living Christ.
他是个面包师
He's a baker.
耶稣升天了
Christ has risen.